Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Courses, Series 6
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Belgium" (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Burma" (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Canada" (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Central America" (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project, Nursing in Charles Dickens Character Sairey Gamp (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in China" (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Cuba" (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in England" (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in France" (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Greece" (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in India" (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Italy" (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Japan" (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Korea" (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Mexico" (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in New Zealand" (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Palestine" (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Puerto Rico" (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in Russia" (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Nursing in South America" (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "Some Biblical Allusions to Care of the Sick" (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "The Life of Clara Barton" (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "The Life of Florence Nightingale" (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "The Life of Linda Richards" (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project "The Life of Violet Schmidt" (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 300: History of Nursing Project, Uniforms - 1500 to 1940s (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Spring 1979 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Fall 1979 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Spring 1980 (1 of 2) (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Spring 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Fall 1980 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Spring 1981 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Fall 1981 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Spring 1982 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 305: Science Concepts for Nursing I - Fall 1982 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1979 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1980 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1981 (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1981 (2 of 2) (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1981 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1981 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1982 (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Spring 1982 (2 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1982 (1 of 2) (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 306: Clinical Nursing I - Fall 1982 (2 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1989 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Spring 1993 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1994 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1995 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1996 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 307: Assertiveness for Nurses - Fall 1997 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 308: Gerontological Nursing - Fall 1980 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1952 to 1953 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1969 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1970 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1973 to Winter 1973-1974 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1974 to 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Winter 1974 to 1975 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1976 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Winter 1976 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Winter to Spring 1977 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1977 to Winter 1978 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1979 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1979 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1996 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Spring 1997 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing - Fall 1997 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing, Archives - 1972 to 1979 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 310: Medical-Surgical Nursing, Tests - 1969 to 1970 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Fall 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Fall 1970 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Spring 1970 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - 1971 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 311: Medical/Surgical Practicum - Fall 1987 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1992 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Spring 1993 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1993 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Spring 1994 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1995 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Spring 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1996 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Spring 1997 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 312: Pathophysiological Basis of Nursing Practice - Fall 1997 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Spring 1990 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Spring 1996 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1996 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Spring 1997 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 313: Mental Health Concepts--Individual and Family - Fall 1997 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Fall 1979 to Spring 1980 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Fall 1980 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Fall 1981 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Spring 1981 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Spring 1982 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 315: Scientific Concepts for Nursing II - Fall 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - 1977 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Fall 1979 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Spring 1980 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Fall 1980 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Spring 1981 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Fall 1981 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Spring 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II - Fall 1982 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 316: Clinical Nursing II, Outreach - Spring 1982 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1965 to Spring 1966 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1966 to Spring 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1969 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Spring 1970 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1973 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Winter 1973 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Spring 1974 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Winter 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Spring 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Spring 1976 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1976 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Winter 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Winter to Spring 1977 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Winter to Spring 1978 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing- Fall 1978 to Spring 1979 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 320: Maternal and Childcare Nursing - Fall 1979 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1987+D1053 to Spring 1988 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1995 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Spring 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1996 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Spring 1997 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations - Fall 1997 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 320: Nursing Concepts--Foundations, Archives - 1950s to 1960s (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - November 1969 to January 1970 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - Spring 1970 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - Fall 1970 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 321: Maternal/Child Nursing Practicum - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1991 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1992 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1992 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1993 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1993 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1994 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1994 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1995 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Spring 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 321: Nursing Practice--Foundations - Fall 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Spring 1970 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Summer 1973 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 330: Survey of Nursing I - Summer 1974 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Spring 1996 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Spring 1997 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment - Fall 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 330: Nursing Concepts and Practice--Health Assessment, Test - 1969 to 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 335: Civil Defense and the Nursing Curriculum - Fall 1954 to Spring 1955 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1973 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1974 to Spring 1975 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1975 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1976 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1977 to Spring 1978 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology - Fall 1978 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 340: Nursing Concepts--Parent-Child - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 340: Pathophysiology, Archives - 1973 to 1978 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 341: Nursing Practice--Parent-Child - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1995 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 342: Nursing Concepts--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1992 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1993 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1993 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1994 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1994 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1995 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1996 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1996 (1 of 2) (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1996 (2 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1997 (1 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Spring 1997 (2 of 2) (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 343: Nursing Practice--Maternity Nursing - Fall 1997 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Spring 1996 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Spring 1997 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 344: Nursing Concepts--Nursing of Children - Fall 1997 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1994 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Spring 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1995 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Spring 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 345: Nursing Practice--Nursing of Children - Fall 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1993 to Spring 1994 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1995 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Spring 1996 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1996 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Spring 1997 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 346: Nursing Concepts--Family and Child Development - Fall 1997 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 350: Effects of Environmental Forces - Fall 1973 (Folder 4)